General Still Photograph Collection
General Still Photograph Collection
- Photographs
  - O'Brien, Margaret - NBC, Person to Person, 5/16/98 (Box 1)
  - O'Connor, Donald - CBS, DuPont Show of the Month: Red Mill, 4/3/58 (Box 1)
  - O'Connor, Donald - CBS, DuPont Show of the Month: Red Mill, 4/4/58 (Box 1)
  - Olsen, Dorothy - NBC, NBC Bandstand (radio broadcast), 6/21/57 (Box 2)
  - O'Meara, Walter - NBC (lighting director) (Box 1)
  - O'Neal, Patrick - NBC, Today is Ours, 6/6/58 (Box 1)
  - Ophir, Shai K. - NBC, Shirley Temple's Storybook: Rumpelstiltskin, 1/17/58 (Box 2)
  - Oreste, Kirk - NBC, Rigoletto, 1/24/58 (Box 2)
  - O'Rourke, Michael - NBC, Tic Tac Dough (shown with 3 other contestants) (Box 1)
  - Owen, Mickey - NBC, Big Moment, 6/14/57 (Box 2)
  - Owens, Jesse - NBC, Big Moment, 6/14/57 (Box 2)
  - Paar, Jack - NBC, Tonight!, 6/14/57 (Box 2)
  - Paar, Jack - NBC, Jack Paar Show, 7/3/58 (Box 1)
  - Page, Geraldine - CBS, Playhouse 90: Portrait of a Murderer, 8/5/58 (Box 1)
  - Page, Patti - CBS, United States Steel Hour: Upbeat, 6/7/57 (Box 2)
  - Page, Patti (Box 2)
  - Paige, Bob - NBC, Bride and Groom, 7/5/57 (Box 2)
  - Paige, Bob - CBS, Big Payoff, 2/3/58 (Box 2)
  - Paige, Robert - NBC, Bride and Groom, 6/14/57 (Box 2)
  - Palmer, Betsy - CBS, I've Got a Secret, 1/14/58 (Box 2)
  - Palmer, Betsy - CBS, Playhouse 90: No Time At All, 1/31/58 (Box 2)
  - Palmer, Bud - NBC, Fight Beat -- Wheaties Sports Page, 6/27/58 (Box 1)
  - Parker, Frank - NBC, Bride and Groom, 6/14/57 (Box 2)
  - Parker, Frank - NBC, Bride and Groom, 7/5/57 (Box 2)
  - Parks, Bert - NBC, NBC Bandstand (radio broadcast), 6/21/57 (Box 2)
  - Parks, Bert - NBC, Bert Parks Bandstand (radio broadcast), 3/28/58 (Box 1)
  - Patrick, Erin - NBC, Today and Jack Paar Show, 4/18/58 (Box 1)
  - Patterson, Floyd - NBC, Heavyweight Championship Fight, 6/28/57 (Box 2)
  - Payne, John - NBC, Restless Gun, 8/9/57 (Box 1)
  - Perkins, Marlin - NBC, Zoo Parade, 1957 (Box 2)
  - Perkins, Marlin - NBC, Zoo Parade, 6/7/57 (Box 2)
  - Peterson, Shirley - NBC (various programs), 6/7/57 (Box 2)
  - Portman, Eric - CBS, DuPont Show of the Month: A Tale of Two Cities, 3/14/58 (Box 1)
  - Poston, Tom - NBC, Steve Allen Show, 1/24/58 (Box 2)
  - Powell, Jane - NBC, Alcoa-Goodyear Anthology, 8/9/57 (Box 1)
  - Prescott, Norm - WBZ/WBZ, Live Five (Box 1)
  - Price, Vincent - CBS, Schlitz Playhouse: Blue Hotel, 7/9/57 (Box 2)
  - Priestley, Tom - NBC, Israel: The Next 10 Years (Box 1)
  - Provost, Jon - CBS, Lassie, 6/14/57 (Box 2)
  - Provost, Jon - CBS, Lassie, 8/14/57 (Box 2)
  - Provost, Jon - CBS, Lassie, 4/8/58 (Box 1)
  - Provost, Jon - CBS, Lassie, 8/28/58 (Box 1)
  - Quinn, Anthony - CBS, Person to Person, 4/16/58 (Box 1)
  - Rafferty, Frances - CBS, Millionaire: Story of Dr. Olivia Grainger, 8/13/57 (Box 2)
  - Rafferty, Frances - CBS, December Bride, 1/16/58 (Box 2)
  - Rains, Claude - CBS, Alfred Hitchcock Presents: Cream of the Jest, 7/18/57 (Box 2)
  - Raitt, John - NBC, Chevy Show, 5/29/58 (Box 1)
  - Ramati, Didi - CBS, Trackdown: Trail, 2/7/58 (Box 2)
  - Rathbone, Basil - CBS, Playhouse of Mystery: Volturio Investigates, 6/17/57 (Box 2)
  - Rayburn, Gene - NBC, Dough Re Mi (Box 1)
  - Re, Peter - ABC, Colby College Fund Drive (shown with Colby College Glee Club) (Box 1)
  - Reason, Rex - CBS, Millionaire: Story of Dr. Olivia Grainger, 8/13/57 (Box 2)
  - Redfield, Billy - NBC, Kitty Foyle, 3/14/58 (Box 1)
  - Redwing, Rodd - NBC, Pardners (Box 1)
  - Reed, Marshall - CBS, Lineup: Pawn Ticket Case, 1/22/58 (Box 2)
  - Reed, Toby - CBS, Top Dollar, 3/21/58 (Box 1)
  - Reed, Toby - CBS, Top Dollar, 4/1/58 (Box 1)
  - Reeves, Maxene - NBC, Queen for a Day, 5/23/58 (Box 1)
  - Reilly, Hugh - CBS, Lassie, 8/28/58 (Box 1)
  - Reuther, Walter - CBS, See It Now: Automation: Weal or Woe, 5/31/57 (Box 2)
  - Richards, Jeff - NBC, Jefferson Drum, 3/28/58 (Box 1)
  - Richards, Jeff - NBC, Jefferson Drum (Box 1)
  - Ritchard, Cyril - CBS, DuPont Show of the Month: Aladdin, 2/3/58 (Box 2)
  - Robbins, Fred - NBC, Haggis Baggis (shown with 7 other hosts), 7/3/58 (Box 1)
  - Robbins, Gale - CBS, Undercurrent: Live Bait, 8/9/57 (Box 1)
  - Robertson, Dale - NBC, Tales of Wells Fargo, 8/2/57 (Box 2)
  - Robertson, Dale - NBC, Tales of Wells Fargo, 7/25/58 (Box 1)
  - Robin, Tina - CBS, Sing Along, 5/23/58 (Box 1)
  - Robinson, Sugar Ray - CBS, Ed Sullivan Show (Box 1)
  - Rodgers, Jimmie - CBS, Beaver Patrol, 3/25/58 (Box 1)
  - Rodman, Vic - CBS, Noah's Ark, 5/9/58 (Box 1)
  - Romero, Cesar - CBS, Schlitz Playhouse: Old Spanish Custom, 8/30/57 (Box 2)
  - Romero, Cesar - NBC, Wagon Train: Honorable Don Charlie, 1/3/58 (Box 2)
  - Rucker, Al - NBC, Dough Re Mi (Box 1)
  - Rudie, Evelyn - CBS, DuPont Show of the Month: Red Mill, 4/3/58 (Box 1)
  - Rudie, Evelyn - CBS, DuPont Show of the Month: Red Mill, 4/4/58 (Box 1)
  - Rule, Janice - NBC, M Squad: Dolly's Bar, 1/17/58 (Box 2)
  - Russell, Autumn - CBS, Bachelor Father: Bentley Loans Out Peter, 1/30/58 (Box 2)
  - Ryan, Robert - NBC, Alcoa-Goodyear Anthology, 8/9/57 (Box 1)
  - Ryan, Robert - CBS, Playhouse 90: Great Gatsby, 6/16/58 (Box 1)
  - Salmi, Albert - CBS, Climax!: Volcano Seat (Box 1)
  - Sandburg, Carl - CBS, Ed Sullivan Show (Box 1)
  - Sanders, David - NBC, From These Roots, 6/13/58 (Box 1)
  - Sands, Billy - CBS, You'll Never Get Rich: Bilko's Honeymoon (shown with others), 3/20/58 (Box 1)
  - Sands, Tommy - NBC, Ford Show, 1/3/58 (Box 2)
  - Sarnoff, Robert W. - NBC (President of NBC) (Box 2)
  - Sas-Jaworsky, Dr., Alexander - CBS, $64,000 Question, 1/17/58 (Box 2)
  - Schaffner, Neil - NBC, Wide Wide World: Sound of Laughter (Box 1)
  - Schneider, Dick - NBC, Dough Re Mi (Box 1)
  - Scott, Lizabeth - CBS, Big Record (Box 1)
  - Scott, Martha - NBC, Modern Romances, 6/7/57 (Box 2)
  - Scott, Patricia - NBC, Dotto (Box 1)
  - Scott, Valerie - CBS, Jack Benny Program (with band in the background), 4/7/58 (Box 1)
  - Scourby, Alexander - NBC, Shirley Temple's Storybook: Sleeping Beauty, 5/16/58 (Box 1)
  - Segura, Pancho - CBS, World's Championship Tennis Matches (from Forest Hill, NY), 6/27/57 (Box 2)
  - Sevareid, Eric - CBS, Conquest: Inertial Guidance: The Ultimate Navigation, 3/28/58 (Box 1)
  - Shatner, William (Box 1)
  - Shatner, William (Box 1)
  - Shaumberg, Lois - NBC, Queen for a Day (Box 1)
  - Shawnee Inn & Country Club, - CBS, Fred Waring Show, 7/24/57 (Box 1)
  - Sheridan, Ann - CBS, Playhouse 90: Without Incident, 8/15/57 (Box 1)
  - Shore, Dinah - NBC, Chevy Show, 1957 (Box 2)
  - Shore, Dinah - NBC, Chevy Show, 8/9/57 (Box 1)
  - Shuster, Frank - CBS, Ed Sullivan Show (Wayne and Shuster comedy team), 4/21/58 (Box 1)
  - Signh, Kuldip - NBC, Shirley Temple's Storybook: Land of Green Ginger, 3/21/58 (Box 1)
  - Silvera, Frank - CBS, Studio One Summer Theater: Guitar, 8/16/57 (Box 2)
  - Silvers, Phil - CBS, You'll Never Get Rich: Doberman's Sister, 7/29/57 (Box 1)
  - Silvers, Phil - CBS, You'll Never Get Rich: Mess Hall Mess (with children), 8/12/1957 (Box 2)
  - Silvers, Phil - CBS, You'll Never Get Rich, 1/30/1958 (Box 2)
  - Silvers, Phil - CBS, You'll Never Get Rich: Bilko's Honeymoon (shown with others), 3/20/58 (Box 1)
  - Silvers, Phil - CBS, Phil Silvers on Broadway (surrounded by dancers and singers), 5/2/58 (Box 1)
  - Silvers, Phil - CBS, You'll Never Get Rich: Colonel's Reunion, 7/3/58 (Box 1)
  - Silvers, Phil - CBS, You'll Never Get Rich: Bilko's Valentine, 7/15/58 (Box 1)
  - Slivers, Phil - CBS, You'll Never Get Rich: Gold Fever, 9/5/58 (Box 1)
  - Silvers, Phil - CBS, You'll Never Get Rich (shown with others) (Box 2)
  - Simmons, Richard - CBS, Sergeant Preston of the Yukon (Box 2)
  - Simms, Frank - CBS, Garry Moore Show, 8/14/57 (Box 2)
  - Simon, Abe - CBS, United States Steel Hour: Side Show, 6/24/57 (Box 2)
  - Singh, Kuldip - NBC, You Bet Your Life (shown with 3 other contestants) (Box 1)
  - Skelton, Red - CBS, Red Skelton Show, 6/6/57 (Box 2)
  - Skelton, Red - CBS, Red Skelton Show, 6/5/58 (Box 1)
  - Skelton, Red - CBS, Red Skelton Show, 5/15/58 (Box 1)
  - Skelton, Red - CBS, Red Skelton Show, 5/22/58 (Box 1)
  - Skylar, Diane - NBC, Tic Tac Dough, 8/9/57 (Box 1)
  - Slezak, Walter - CBS, Beaver Patrol, 3/25/58 (Box 1)
  - Sloane, Everett - CBS, Playhouse 90: Massacre at Sand Creek (shown with others), 7/3/57 (Box 2)
  - Sloane, Everett - NBC, No Warning!: Ashley and Son, 3/28/58 (Box 1)
  - Smith, Howard - CBS, Garry Moore Show, 8/14/57 (Box 2)
  - Smith, Kate (Kate Smith's Birthday Party), 6/10/57 (Box 2)
  - Smith, Kent - CBS, General Electric Theater: Last Town Car, 2/4/58 (Box 2)
  - St. John, Howard - NBC, Investigator, 5/29/58 (Box 1)
  - St. John, Howard - CBS, You'll Never Get Rich: Colonel's Reunion, 7/3/58 (Box 1)
  - St. John, Jill - CBS, No Second Helping, 6/13/58 (Box 1)
  - Stafford, Marian - NBC, Treasure Hunt, 7/3/58 (Box 1)
  - Stafford, Marian - NBC, Treasure Hunt (shown with 7 other women), 7/25/58 (Box 1)
  - Stafford, Marion - NBC, Tic Tac Dough, 8/9/57 (Box 1)
  - Stanwyck, Barbara - NBC, Decision: Sudden Silence, 7/18/58 (Box 1)
  - Stapleton, Maureen - CBS, Seven Lively Arts: Blast in Centralia #5 (other spelling "Centraliz"), 1/21/58 (Box 2)
  - Steele, Karen - CBS, Millionaire, 8/29/58 (Box 1)
  - Sterling, Robert - ABC, Love That Jill: They Went Thataway (Box 2)
  - Stevens, Mark - CBS, Schlitz Playhouse: Sporting Chance, 8/16/57 (Box 1)
  - Stevens, Mark - CBS, Destiny: Sporting Chance, 7/31/58 (Box 1)
  - Stevens, Terri - NBC, Bert Parks Bandstand (radio broadcast), 3/28/58 (Box 1)
  - Stevens, Terri - NBC, Bert Parks' Bandstand (radio broadcast), 4/25/58 (Box 1)
  - !Storm, Gale - CBS, Gale Storm Show: Oh! Susanna, 8/22/57 (Box 1)
  - Storm, Gale - CBS, Gale Storm Show: Lovey-Dovey, 7/25/58 (Box 1)
  - Storm, Gale - CBS, Gale Storm Show (Box 1)
  - Straight, Beatrice (Box 1)
  - Stratton, Chester - CBS, Playhouse 90: Confession, 6/28/57 (Box 2)
  - Stratton, Chester - NBC, Wagon Train: Annie MacGregor Story, 1/10/58 (Box 2)
  - Stritch, Elaine - CBS, DuPont Show of the Month: Red Mill, 4/3/58 (Box 1)
  - Sullivan, Barry - CBS, Playhouse 90: Ain't No Time for Glory, 6/7/57 (Box 2)
  - Sullivan, Barry - CBS, Playhouse 90: Ain't No Time for Glory (with several men in background), 8/22/57 (Box 2)
  - Sullivan, Barry - CBS, Playhouse 90: Nightmare at Ground Zero, 5/2/58 (Box 1)
  - Sullivan, Ed - CBS, Ed Sullivan Show, 6/10/57 (Box 2)
  - Sullivan, Ed - CBS, Fred Waring Show, 7/12/57 (Box 2)
  - Sullivan, Ed - CBS, Ed Sullivan Show, 1/29/58 (Box 2)
  - Sullivan, Ed - CBS, Ed Sullivan Show, 4/21/58 (Box 1)
  - Sullivan, Ed - CBS, Ed Sullivan Show, 6/3/58 (Box 1)
  - Sullivan, Ed - CBS, Ed Sullivan Show, 6/3/58 (Box 1)
  - Sullivan, Ed - CBS, Ed Sullivan Show (Box 1)
  - Sullivan, Ed - CBS, Ed Sullivan Show (Box 1)
  - Sullivan, Ed - CBS, Ed Sullivan Show (Box 1)
  - Sullivan, Ed - CBS, Ed Sullivan Show (Box 1)
  - Sullivan, Ed - CBS, Ed Sullivan Show (Box 1)
  - Sullivan, Ed - CBS, Ed Sullivan Show (Box 1)
  - Sullivan, Ed - CBS, Ed Sullivan Show (Box 1)
  - Sullivan, Ed - CBS, Ed Sullivan Show (Box 1)
  - Sullivan, Ed - CBS, Ed Sullivan Show (Box 1)
  - Sullivan, Ed - CBS, Ed Sullivan Show (Box 1)
  - Sullivan, Ed - CBS, Ed Sullivan Show (Box 1)
  - Sullivan, Ed - CBS, Ed Sullivan Show (Box 1)
  - Sullivan, Ed - CBS, Ed Sullivan Show (Box 1)
  - Sullivan, Liam - NBC, Shirley Temple's Storybook: Nightingale, 1/24/58 (Box 2)
  - Sullivan, Liam - NBC, Shirley Temple's Storybook: Nightingale, 1/24/58 (Box 2)
  - Sullivan, Liam - NBC, Shirley Temple's Storybook: Nightingale, 1/24/58 (Box 2)
  - Sullivan, Liam - NBC, Shirley Temple's Storybook: Nightingale (Box 2)
  - Swanson, Janet - CBS, Studio One In Hollywood: Mrs. 'Arris Goes to Paris, 3/28/58 (Box 1)
  - Sweeney, Bob - CBS, Climax!: Push-Button Giant (Box 1)
  - Swiacki, Bill - NBC, Big Moment, 6/14/57 (Box 2)
  - Tai, Thomas - CBS, Beaver Patrol, 3/25/58 (Box 1)
  - Talbot, Lyle - ABC, Adventures of Ozzie and Harriet: Safe (Box 2)
  - Tamplin, Bob - CBS, Ed Sullivan Show (Box 1)
  - Tamplin, Bob - CBS, Ed Sullivan Show (Box 1)
  - Tandy, Jessica - CBS, Alfred Hitchcock Presents, 5/29/58 (Box 1)
  - Taylor, Joan - NBC, Wagon Train: A Man Called Horse, 1/24/58 (Box 2)
  - Terrace, Joan - CBS, Let's Take a Trip: Coney Island Aquarium (with penguins), 7/24/57 (Box 2)
  - Terrace, Joan - CBS, Let's Take a Trip: S.S. United States, 1/22/58 (Box 2)
  - Thomas, Danny - CBS, Danny Thomas Show, 2/7/58 (Box 2)
  - Thomas, Lowell - CBS, High Adventure with Lowell Thomas, 2/6/58 (Box 2)
  - Thomas, Lowell - CBS, High Adventure with Lowell Thomas, 3/28/58 (Box 1)
  - Thompson, Marshall - CBS, Playhouse 90: Blackwell Story, 7/19/57 (Box 2)
  - Thompson, Rex - NBC, Shirley Temple's Storybook: Little Lame Prince, 6/27/58 (Box 1)
  - Thompson, Rex - NBC, Shirley Temple's Storybook: Little Lame Prince, 7/9/58 (Box 1)
  - Thurman, Tedi - NBC, Monitor (radio broadcast), 8/2/57 (Box 2)
  - Thurman, Tedi - NBC, Monitor (radio broadcast, a.k.a. Miss Monitor), 4/11/58 (Box 1)
  - Toigo, Alfred - NBC, No Warning!: Ashley and Son, 3/28/58 (Box 1)
  - Tone, Franchot - CBS, Studio One In Hollywood: Ticket to Tahiti, 5/26/58 (Box 1)
  - Tone, Franchot - CBS, Playhouse 90: Thundering Wave, 6/25/58 (Box 1)
  - Tone, Franchot - CBS, Playhouse 90: Bitter Heritage, 7/22/58 (Box 1)
  - Toomey, Marilyn - NBC, Tic Tac Dough, 8/9/57 (Box 1)
  - Toomey, Marilyn - NBC, Win With a Winner, 7/11/58 (Box 1)
  - Towers, Constance - CBS, Schlitz Playhouse: Sporting Chance, 8/2/57 (Box 2)
  - Towers, Constance - CBS, Schlitz Playhouse: Sporting Chance, 8/16/57 (Box 1)
  - Towers, Constance - CBS, Destiny: Sporting Chance, 7/31/58 (Box 1)
  - Townes, Harry - CBS, Climax!: The Time of the Hanging (Box 1)
  - Towsen, Johnny - CBS, Beaver Patrol, 3/25/58 (Box 1)
  - Truman, Harry S. - CBS, See It Now: From Precinct To President, 1/20/58 (Box 2)
  - Trundy, Natalie - CBS, Studio One Summer Theater: Mother Bit, 5/31/57 (Box 2)
  - Tully, Tom - CBS, Lineup: Samuel Bradford Case, 1/20/58 (Box 2)
  - Tully, Tom - CBS, Lineup, 9/5/58 (Box 1)
  - Tuttle, Roger - NBC, Dough Re Mi (Box 1)
  - Valli, June - NBC, Andy Williams-June Valli Show, 6/7/57 (Box 2)
  - Van Doren, John - NBC, High-Low, 7/12/57 (Box 2)
  - Van Dyke, Dick - CBS, You'll Never Get Rich: Bilko's Cousin (shown with 6 others), 1/28/58 (Box 1)
  - Vanderbilt, Gloria (Box 1)
  - Vanderveen, Joyce - NBC, Meet McGraw: Ballerina, 7/5/57 (Box 2)
  - Varden, Norma - CBS, Playhouse of Mystery: Volturio Investigates, 6/17/57 (Box 2)
  - Venturi, Ken - CBS, Master's Golf Tournament, 3/17/58 (Box 1)
  - Vickers, Martha - CBS, Playhouse 90: Galvanized Yankee, 6/17/58 (Box 1)
  - Vitina, Dolores - CBS, Schlitz Playhouse: Curfew at Midnight, 6/10/58 (Box 1)
  - Vito, Annette - NBC, Bride and Groom, 6/28/57 (Box 2)
  - Vohs, Joan - CBS, Millionaire, 9/4/58 (Box 1)
  - Voland, Herb - CBS, Studio One Summer Theater: A Matter of Guilt, 6/28/57 (Box 2)
  - von Nardroff, Elfrida - NBC, Twenty One (shown with 3 other contestants) (Box 1)
  - Voorhees, Donald - NBC, Telephone Hour (radio broadcast), 4/18/58 (Box 1)
  - Walker, Carol - NBC, Haggis Baggis (shown with 7 other women), 7/25/58 (Box 1)
  - Walsh, Jimmy - CBS, Let's Take a Trip: Coney Island Aquarium (with penguins), 7/24/57 (Box 2)
  - Walsh, Jimmy - CBS, Let's Take a Trip: S.S. United States, 1/22/58 (Box 2)
  - Walters, Nancy - CBS, Strike It Rich, 7/8/57 (Box 2)
  - Ward, Victoria - CBS, Playhouse 90: So Soon To Die, 7/12/57 (Box 2)
  - Waring, Fred - CBS, Fred Waring Show, 7/12/57 (Box 2)
  - Washburn, Beverly - NBC, Shirley Temple's Storybook: Rip Van Winkle (with dog, Wolf) (Box 1)
  - Wayne, David - CBS, Big Record The, 8/21/57 (Box 2)
  - Wayne, Fredd - NBC, Wagon Train: Annie MacGregor Story, 1/10/58 (Box 2)
  - Wayne, John - CBS, Ed Sullivan Show (Wayne and Shuster comedy team), 4/21/58 (Box 1)
  - Weaver, Dennis - CBS, Climax!: Burst of Fire (Box 2)
  - Webb, Jack - NBC, Dragnet, 1957 (Box 2)
  - Webb, Jack - NBC, Dragnet, 4/18/58 (Box 1)
  - Webb, Jack - NBC, Dragnet, 4/25/58 (Box 1)
  - Webb, Jack - CBS, Noah's Ark, 5/9/58 (Box 1)
  - Welles, Rebecca - NBC, Californians: Bridal Bouquet, 5/16/58 (Box 1)
  - White, Betty - ABC, Betty White Show (Box 2)
  - White, Betty - ABC, Betty White Show (Box 2)
  - White, Betty - ABC, Betty White Show (Box 2)
  - White, Pat - NBC, Treasure Hunt, 7/12/57 (Box 2)
  - Whiting, Barbara - CBS, Those Whiting Girls, 6/14/57 (Box 2)
  - Whiting, Barbara - CBS, Those Whiting Girls, 6/14/57 (Box 2)
  - Whiting, Barbara - CBS, Those Whiting Girls, 7/16/57 (Box 2)
  - Whiting, Margaret - CBS, Those Whiting Girls, 6/14/57 (Box 2)
  - Whiting, Margaret - CBS, Those Whiting Girls, 6/14/57 (Box 2)
  - Whiting, Margaret - CBS, Those Whiting Girls, 7/16/57 (Box 2)
  - Whitmore, James - NBC, Decision: Fear Has Many Faces, 8/8/58 (Box 1)
  - Wilcox, Collin - CBS, Show of the Month: Member of the Wedding, 5/26/58 (Box 1)
  - Wilcox, Collin - CBS, Show of the Month: Member of the Wedding, 5/29/58 (Box 1)
  - Wilde, Cornel - ABC, Betty White Show (Box 2)
  - Wilder, Nancy - NBC, Modern Romances, 6/14/57 (Box 2)
  - Wilding, Michael - CBS, Playhouse 90: Verdict of Three, 4/11/58 (Box 1)
  - Williams, Andy - NBC, Andy Williams-June Valli Show, 6/7/57 (Box 2)
  - Williams, John - NBC, Hallmark Hall of Fame: Dial 'M' for Murder, 4/4/58 (Box 1)
  - Williams, Mack - ABC, Adventures of Ozzie and Harriet: Rick's Chemistry Grade (Box 1)
  - Winston, Helen - CBS, Dotto, 4/10/58 (Box 1)
  - Winston, Lois - NBC, Wide Wide World (head of Central Research), 8/16/57 (Box 2)
  - Wiseman, Joseph - CBS, Schlitz Playhouse: False Alarm, 7/25/58 (Box 1)
  - Wiss, Doris - NBC, Bob Cummings Show, 1/17/58 (Box 2)
  - Wiss, Doris - NBC, Lucky Partners!, 7/11/58 (Box 1)
  - Wiss, Doris - NBC, Lucky Partners! (shown with 7 other women), 7/25/58 (Box 1)
  - Wolff, Perry - CBS, Air Power, 5/1/58 (Box 1)
  - Wong, Anna May - CBS, Climax!: Deadly Tattoo (Box 1)
  - Woods, Donald - CBS, Hotel Cosmopolitan, 8/9/57 (Box 1)
  - Wray, Johnny - CBS, Ed Sullivan Show (Box 1)
  - Wray, Johnny - CBS, Ed Sullivan Show (Box 1)
  - Wright, Teresa - CBS, Playhouse 90: Edge of Innocence, 7/1/58 (Box 1)
  - Wyler, Gretchen - NBC, Bob Crosby Show, 5/23/58 (Box 1)
  - Wyler, Gretchen - NBC, Bob Crosby Show, 7/11/58 (Box 1)
  - Wyman, Jane - NBC, Jane Wyman Show, 8/9/57 (Box 1)
  - Wynn, Ed (Kate Smith's Birthday Party), 6/10/57 (Box 2)
  - Wynn, Keenan - NBC, M Squad, 5/23/58 (Box 1)
  - York, Dick - CBS, Millionaire, 9/4/58 (Box 1)
  - Yorkin, Alan "Bud" - NBC, Ford Show (Box 1)
  - Young, Loretta - NBC, Loretta Young Show, 1957 (Box 2)
  - Young, Loretta - NBC, Young Show: Day of Rest, 5/2/58 (Box 1)
  - Young, Robert - NBC, Father Knows Best, 1957 (Box 2)
  - Zwillinger, Jack - NBC (NBC photographer), 6/17/58 (Box 1)
  - Lassie - CBS, Lassie, 6/14/57 (Box 2)
  - Lassie - CBS, Lassie, 8/28/58 (Box 1)
  - Meteors - NBC, Bell System Science Series: Unchained Goddess (animated goddess of weather with model), 1/24/58 (Box 2)
  - [no name] - CBS, Twentieth Century: Face of Crime (inmate of Bordentown Reformatory), 1/15/58 (Box 2)
  - [no name] - CBS, See it Now: Atomic Time-Table, Part II (camera crew), 3/19/58 (Box 1)
  - [no name] - CBS, Search: State University of Iowa, Speech Therapy (woman doctor and patient), 5/20/58 (Box 1)
  - [no name] - CBS, Verdict is Yours (judge, attorney and witnesses shown), 6/17/58 (Box 1)